Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1949-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 3: Photographs, 1950-2005(Boxes 589-639)
  - Subseries 3.1: Production photographs, 1950-2005
    - Enemy of the People, 1975-1976 (Box 596, Folder 14)
    - Enrico IV, 1964 (Box 596, Folder 15)
    - Production Photos-Enrico IV, 1987-1988 (Box 596, Folder 16)
    - Enrico IV, 1988-1989 (Box 596, Folder 17)
    - Epitaph for George Dillon, 1959 (Box 596, Folder 18)
    - Execution of Justice, 1984-1985 (Box 596, Folder 19)
    - Fences, 1989-1990 (Box 596, Folder 20)
    - Production Photos-Fences: Photos by George de Vincent, 1989-1990 (Box 597, Folder 1)
    - The Firebrand, 1950-1951 (Box 597, Folder 2)
    - The Flying Karamazov Brothers, 1980-1981 (Box 597, Folder 3)
    - The Flying Karamazov Brothers, 1986 (Box 597, Folder 4)
    - The Fool Show, 1988-1989 (Box 597, Folder 5)
    - Fools Fire, 1984 (Box 597, Folder 6)
    - Forever Yours, Marie-Lou, 1976-1977 (Box 597, Folder 7)
    - The Foursome, 1972-1973 (Box 597, Folder 8)
    - The Front Page, 1958 (Box 597, Folder 9)
    - Galileo, 1964 (Box 597, Folder 10)
    - Galileo, 1980-1981 (Box 597, Folder 11)
    - The Gangs All Here, 1960 (Box 597, Folder 12)
    - Gemini, 1978 (Box 597, Folder 13)
    - Geniuses, 1982-1983 (Box 597, Folder 14)
    - Gertrude Stein Gertrude Stein Gertrude Stein, 1980 (Box 597, Folder 15)
    - The Girl on the Via Flaminia, 1957 (Box 597, Folder 16)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1951 (Box 597, Folder 17)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1951 (Box 597, Folder 18)
    - Glen Garry Glenn Ross, 1987 (Box 597, Folder 19)
    - God Bless You, Mr. Rosewater, 1987 (Box 597, Folder 20)
    - Golden Boy, 1954-1955 (Box 598, Folder 1)
    - Good Person of Setzuan, 1985-4986 (Box 598, Folder 2)
    - Gospel at Colonus, 1984-1985 (Box 598, Folder 3)
    - The Great Ladies of Blues and Jazz, 1987 (Box 598, Folder 4)
    - The Great White Hope, 1966-1967 (Box 598, Folder 5)
    - The Great White Hope-Negatives, 1967-1968 (Box 598, Folder 6)
    - Hamlet, 1978 (Box 598, Folder 7)
    - Happy End, 1983-1984 (Box 598, Folder 8)
    - Happy End, 1983-1984 (Box 598, Folder 9)
    - Hasty Heart, 1951-1952 (Box 598, Folder 10)
    - He Who Gets Slapped, 1965 (Box 598, Folder 11)
    - Heartbreak House, 1965 (Box 598, Folder 12)
    - Heartbreak House, 1975-1976 (Box 598, Folder 13)
    - Production Photos-Heartbreak House Photos by Shelley Langston, 1986-1987 (Box 598, Folder 14)
    - Heartbreak House, 1987 (Box 599, Folder 1)
    - A History of American Film, 1987 (Box 599, Folder 2)
    - The Hollow, 1958 (Box 599, Folder 3)
    - Home, 1982-1983 (Box 599, Folder 4)
    - Horatio, 1973-1974 (Box 599, Folder 5)
    - Horatio-Negatives, 1973-1974 (Box 599, Folder 6)
    - The Hostage (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 599, Folder 7)
    - The Hostage (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 599, Folder 8)
    - The Hostage, 1972-1973 (Box 599, Folder 9)
    - Hotel Paradiso, 1963 (Box 599, Folder 10)
    - The House of Blue Leaves, 1971-1972 (Box 599, Folder 11)
    - The Iceman Cometh, 1960 (Box 599, Folder 12)
    - The Iceman Cometh, 1968 (Box 599, Folder 13)
    - Idiots Delight, 1979 (Box 599, Folder 14)
    - The Imaginary Invalid, 1982-1983 (Box 599, Folder 15)
    - The Immigrant: A Hamilton County Album, 1987 (Box 599, Folder 16)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1951 (Box 599, Folder 17)
    - Production Photo-The Importance of Being Ernest, 1983-1984 (Box 600, Folder 1)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1983-1984 (Box 600, Folder 2)
    - In Celebration, 1973-1974 (Box 600, Folder 3)
    - Indians, 1968-1969 (Box 600, Folder 4)
    - Inherit the Wind, 1973-1974 (Box 600, Folder 5)
    - In the Zone, 1961 (Box 600, Folder 6)
    - The Inspector General, 1951 (Box 600, Folder 7)
    - The Inspector General, 1967 (Box 600, Folder 8)
    - Isn't It Romantic, 1984-1985 (Box 600, Folder 9)
    - Production Photos-Isn't It Romantic, 1984-1985 (Box 600, Folder 10)
    - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living In Paris, 1969 (Box 600, Folder 11)
    - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, 1987-1988 (Box 600, Folder 12)
    - Production Photos-Joe Turner, 1987-1988 (Box 600, Folder 13)
    - Julius Caesar, 1951 (Box 600, Folder 14)
    - Julius Caesar, 1974-1975 (Box 600, Folder 15)
    - Juno and the Paycock, 1957-1958 (Box 601, Folder 1)
    - Juno and the Paycock, 1990 (Box 601, Folder 2)
    - K-2, 1982 (Box 601, Folder 3)
    - Kean, 1981 (Box 601, Folder 4)
    - King Lear, 1969 (Box 601, Folder 5)
    - Krapp's Last Tape, 1961 (Box 601, Folder 6)
    - Ladder to the Moon, 1951 (Box 601, Folder 7)
    - Lady Precious Stream, 1952-1953 (Box 601, Folder 8)
    - The Lady's Not for Burning, 1959 (Box 601, Folder 9)
    - The Last Meeting of The Knights of White Magnolia, 1974-1975 (Box 601, Folder 10)
    - Les Blancs, 1987-1988 (Box 601, Folder 11)
    - Les Blancs, 1987-1988 (Box 601, Folder 12)
    - Leonce and Lena, 1973-1974 (Box 601, Folder 13)
    - The Lesson, 1966 (Box 601, Folder 14)
    - A Lesson from Aloes, 1981-1982 (Box 601, Folder 15)
    - A Lie of the Mind, 1988-1989 (Box 601, Folder 16)
    - Light Up the Sky, 1987-1988 (Box 601, Folder 17)
    - Production Photos-Light Up the Sky: Photos by George de Vincent, 1987-1988 (Box 601, Folder 18)
    - The Littlest Circle, 1961-1962 (Box 601, Folder 19)
    - The Lonesome Trains and Hard Traveling, 1965 (Box 601, Folder 20)
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night, 1965 (Box 601, Folder 21)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night, 1975-1976 (Box 601, Folder 22)
    - A Look at the Fifties, 1972-1973 (Box 602, Folder 1)
    - A Look at the Fifties, 1972-1973 (Box 602, Folder 2)
    - Look Back in Anger, 1967 (Box 602, Folder 3)
    - Loose Ends, 1978-1979 (Box 602, Folder 4)
    - The Lower Depths, 1976-1977 (Box 602, Folder 5)
    - Macbeth, 1966 (Box 602, Folder 6)
    - Mademoiselle Colombe, 1958 (Box 602, Folder 7)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot, 1961 (Box 602, Folder 8)
    - Madwoman of Chaillot-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1961 (Box 602, Folder 9)
    - The Magistrate, 1967 (Box 602, Folder 10)
    - Major Barbara, 1959 (Box 602, Folder 11)
    - Major Barbara, 1967 (Box 602, Folder 12)
    - Major Barbara, 1981-1982 (Box 602, Folder 13)
    - Man and Superman, 1961 (Box 602, Folder 14)
    - Man and Superman, 1984-1985 (Box 602, Folder 15)
    - Man of Destiny, 1957 (Box 602, Folder 16)
    - The Man Who Came To Dinner, 1980-1981 (Box 602, Folder 17)
    - The Man Who Came To Dinner, 1989-1990 (Box 602, Folder 18)
    - Marat Sade, 1969 (Box 603, Folder 1)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo, 1986 (Box 603, Folder 2)
    - Measure for Measure, 1986 (Box 603, Folder 3)
    - Measure for Measure, 1986-1987 (Box 603, Folder 4)
    - Merrily We Roll Along, 1989-1990 (Box 603, Folder 5)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1981-1982 (Box 603, Folder 6)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1989-1990 (Box 603, Folder 7)
    - Misalliance, 1962 (Box 603, Folder 8)
    - Misalliance-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1961-1962 (Box 603, Folder 9)
    - The Miser, 1955 (Box 603, Folder 10)
    - Mississippi Delta, 1990-1991 (Box 603, Folder 11)
    - The Moon in the Yellow River, 1962 (Box 603, Folder 12)
    - Moon of the Yellow River-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1961-1962 (Box 603, Folder 13)
    - Mother Courage, 1970-1971 (Box 603, Folder 14)
    - Monteith and Rand, 1982-1983 (Box 603, Folder 15)
    - A Month in the Country, 1958-1959 (Box 603, Folder 16)
    - Moonchildren, 1971-1972 (Box 603, Folder 17)
    - The Mousetrap, 1953 (Box 603, Folder 18)
    - Mr. Arcularis, 1951 (Box 604, Folder 1)
    - Mummenschanz, 1979-1980 (Box 604, Folder 2)
    - My Children, My Africa, 1990-1991 (Box 604, Folder 3)
    - My Heart is in the Highlands, 1953 (Box 604, Folder 4)
    - National Health, 1977 (Box 604, Folder 5)
    - Nevis Mountain Dew, 1979 (Box 604, Folder 6)
    - Night Mother, 1985-1986 (Box 604, Folder 7)
    - Nightclub Cantata, 1977 (Box 604, Folder 8)
    - The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail, 1970-1971 (Box 604, Folder 9)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour, 1978-1979 (Box 604, Folder 10)
    - No Place to be Somebody, 1969-1970 (Box 604, Folder 11)
    - Nat X, 1973 (Box 604, Folder 12)
    - Nothing Sacred, 1988-1989 (Box 604, Folder 13)
    - Oba Koso, circa 1975 (Box 604, Folder 14)
    - Of Mice and Men, 1950 (Box 604, Folder 15)
    - Oh What A Lovely War, 1966 (Box 604, Folder 16)
    - Old Times, 1985-1986 (Box 604, Folder 17)
    - Old Times, 1985-1986 (Box 604, Folder 18)
    - On The Razzle, 1982-1983 (Box 604, Folder 19)
    - On The Town, 1988-1989 (Box 604, Folder 20)
    - On The Way Home-Stephen Wade, 1989-1991 (Box 604, Folder 21)
    - Once Grand the Black (3 short plays), 1958 (Box 604, Folder 22)
    - Once in a Lifetime, 1962 (Box 604, Folder 23)
    - Once in a Lifetime-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1962-1963 (Box 604, Folder 24)
    - Once in a Lifetime, 1976 (Box 605, Folder 1)
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, 1972-1973 (Box 605, Folder 2)
    - One Mo Time, 1980 (Box 605, Folder 3)
    - Othello, 1963 (Box 605, Folder 4)
    - Othello-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1962-1963 (Box 605, Folder 5)
    - Our Town, 1953 (Box 605, Folder 6)
    - Our Town, 1973-1974 (Box 605, Folder 7)
    - Our Town, 1990-1991 (Box 605, Folder 8)
    - Ourselves Alone, 1987 (Box 605, Folder 9)
    - Pantagleize, 1971-1972 (Box 605, Folder 10)
    - Pantomime, 1980-1981 (Box 605, Folder 11)
    - Passion Play, 1984-1985 (Box 605, Folder 12)
    - The Philadelphia Story, 1985-1986 (Box 605, Folder 13)
    - Production Photos-Philadelphia Story Photos by George de Vincent, 1985-1986 (Box 605, Folder 14)
    - A Phoenix Too Frequent, 1953 (Box 605, Folder 15)
    - Pictures in the Hallway, 1958 (Box 605, Folder 16)
    - The Piggy Bank, 1986-1987 (Box 605, Folder 17)
    - Production Photos-Piggy Bank Photos by George de Vincent, 1986-1987 (Box 606, Folder 1)
    - Play, That Time, Footfalls, 1976-1977 (Box 606, Folder 2)
    - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1989 (Box 606, Folder 3)
    - The Playboy of the Western World, 1951 (Box 606, Folder 4)
    - Plenty, 1980 (Box 606, Folder 5)
    - The Plough and the Stars, 1959 (Box 606, Folder 6)
    - Portrait of a Madonna, 1957 (Box 606, Folder 7)
    - Poor Bitos, 1967 (Box 606, Folder 8)
    - The Prisoner, 1957 (Box 606, Folder 9)
    - Project Immortality, 1966 (Box 606, Folder 10)
    - A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All, 1972-1973 (Box 606, Folder 11)
    - Pueblo, 1970-1971 (Box 606, Folder 12)
    - Pygmalion, 1950-1951 (Box 606, Folder 13)
    - Pygmalion, 1990-1991 (Box 606, Folder 14)
    - Quartermaine's Terms, 1983-1984 (Box 606, Folder 15)
    - Rain, 1955 (Box 606, Folder 16)
    - Raisin, 1972-1973 (Box 606, Folder 17)
    - Real Estate, 1984-1985 (Box 606, Folder 18)
    - The Regard of Flight, 1985-1986 (Box 606, Folder 19)
    - The Rehearsal, 1964-1965 (Box 607, Folder 1)
    - Relatively Speaking, 1973-1974 (Box 607, Folder 2)
    - The Resistable Rise of Arturo Ui, 1973-1974 (Box 607, Folder 3)
    - The Resistable Rise of Arturo Ui-Negatives, 1973-1974 (Box 607, Folder 4)
    - Restoration, 1985-1986 (Box 607, Folder 5)
    - Ring Round The Moon, 1960 (Box 607, Folder 6)
    - Ring Round The Moon, 1988-1989 (Box 607, Folder 7)
    - The Rivals, 1968 (Box 607, Folder 8)
    - Rivers and Ravines, 1988 (Box 607, Folder 9)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1958 (Box 607, Folder 10)
    - Room Service, 1954 (Box 607, Folder 11)
    - Room Service, 1968 (Box 607, Folder 12)
    - The Ruling Class, 1970-1971 (Box 607, Folder 13)
    - Saint Joan, 1966 (Box 607, Folder 14)
    - Saint Joan, 1976 (Box 607, Folder 15)
    - Saturday, Sunday, Monday, 1976-1977 (Box 607, Folder 16)
    - The Scarecrow, 1950-1951 (Box 607, Folder 17)
    - School for Scandal, 1952 (Box 607, Folder 18)
    - The School for Wives, 1950-1951 (Box 607, Folder 19)
    - Screenplay, 1982-1983 (Box 608, Folder 1)
    - The Seagull, 1990-1991 (Box 608, Folder 2)
    - Sergeant Musgrave's Dance, 1966 (Box 608, Folder 3)
    - The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window, 1970-1971 (Box 608, Folder 4)
    - Silent Night, Lonely Night, 1961 (Box 608, Folder 5)
    - The Sing Ling Circus, 1962-1963 (Box 608, Folder 6)
    - Sizwe Banzi Is Dead and The Island, 1974-1975 (Box 608, Folder 7)
    - Sizwe Banzi Is Dead and The Island-Negatives, 1974-1975 (Box 608, Folder 8)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1961 (Box 608, Folder 9)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1988-1989 (Box 608, Folder 10)
    - She Stoops to Conquer, 1950-1951 (Box 608, Folder 11)
    - She Stoops to Conquer, 1990-1991 (Box 608, Folder 12)
    - Shavings: An Evening of Short Show, 1959 (Box 608, Folder 13)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1966 (Box 608, Folder 14)
    - Stand-Up Tragedy, 1989-1990 (Box 608, Folder 15)
    - Starting Here Starting Now, 1977 (Box 608, Folder 16)
    - Status Quo Vadis, 1971-1972 (Box 608, Folder 17)
    - Still Life, 1982-1983 (Box 608, Folder 18)
    - Stray Dogs, 1985-1986 (Box 609, Folder 1)
    - Streamers, 1976-1977 (Box 609, Folder 2)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire, 1977-1978 (Box 609, Folder 3)
    - The Suicide...A Comedy, 1981 (Box 609, Folder 4)
    - Summer of the 17th Doll, 1958 (Box 609, Folder 5)
    - The Tale of Lear, 1988-1989 (Box 609, Folder 6)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods, 1978 (Box 609, Folder 7)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 1950 (Box 609, Folder 8)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 1964 (Box 609, Folder 9)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 1985-1986 (Box 609, Folder 10)
    - Production Photos-Taming of the Shrew, 1986 (Box 609, Folder 11)
    - Tartuffe, 1954 (Box 609, Folder 12)
    - Tartuffe, 1984 (Box 609, Folder 13)
    - Teibele and Her Demon, 1979-1980 (Box 609, Folder 14)
    - The Tempest, 1984-1985 (Box 610, Folder 1)
    - The Tenth Man, 1967-1968 (Box 610, Folder 2)
    - Theater Carnival, 1953 (Box 610, Folder 3)
    - The Men on a Horse, 1952 (Box 610, Folder 4)
    - Three Men on a Horse, 1959 (Box 610, Folder 5)
    - Three Men on a Horse, 1973-1974 (Box 610, Folder 6)
    - The Three Penny Opera, 1963 (Box 610, Folder 7)
    - The Three Penny Opera, 1968-1969 (Box 610, Folder 8)
    - The Three Penny Opera-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1960s (Box 610, Folder 9)
    - Three Sisters, 1957 (Box 610, Folder 10)
    - Three Sisters, 1966 (Box 610, Folder 11)
    - Three Sisters, 1983-1984 (Box 611, Folder 1)
    - Tiger at the Gate, 1961 (Box 611, Folder 2)
    - Time of Your Life, 1962 (Box 611, Folder 3)
    - Time of Your Life-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1961-1962 (Box 611, Folder 4)
    - A Ragtime Revue, 1978-1979 (Box 611, Folder 5)
    - Tom, 1973-1974 (Box 611, Folder 6)
    - Tomfoolery, 1981-1982 (Box 611, Folder 7)
    - Tonight at 8:30, 1952 (Box 611, Folder 8)
    - Tot Family, 1975-1976 (Box 611, Folder 9)
    - Tricks, 1971-1972 (Box 611, Folder 10)
    - Twelfth Night, 1951-1952 (Box 611, Folder 11)
    - Twelfth Night, 1971-1972 (Box 611, Folder 12)
    - Twelve Angry Men, 1963 (Box 611, Folder 13)
    - The Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1990-1991 (Box 611, Folder 14)
    - Uncle Vanya, 1963 (Box 611, Folder 15)
    - Uncle Vanya-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1961-1962 (Box 611, Folder 16)
    - Under Milkwood-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1962-1963 (Box 611, Folder 17)
    - Under Milkwood-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1962-1963 (Box 611, Folder 18)
    - Undiscovered Country, 1981-1982 (Box 611, Folder 19)
    - Unknown Production Photos, 1960s (Box 611, Folder 20)
    - Uptight, 1971-1972 (Box 612, Folder 1)
    - Various production photographs, 1993-2005 (Box 612, Folder 2)
    - The View from the Bridge, 1956 (Box 612, Folder 3)
    - Vivisections from the Blown Mind, 1990-1991 (Box 612, Folder 4)
    - Volpone, 1962 (Box 612, Folder 5)
    - Volpone-George de Vincent Production Photos, 1962-1963 (Box 612, Folder 6)
    - Stephen Wade: Banjo Dancing, 1980s (Box 612, Folder 7)
    - Stephen Wade: On the Way Home, 1988-1989 (Box 612, Folder 8)
    - Waiting for Godot, 1976 (Box 612, Folder 9)
    - A Walk in the Woods, 1988-1989 (Box 612, Folder 10)
    - The Wall, 1964 (Box 612, Folder 11)
    - Weird in the Welleiron, 1966 (Box 612, Folder 12)
    - Mr. Welh and Jessey Jim, 1964 (Box 612, Folder 13)
    - What the Butler Saw, 1970-1971 (Box 614, Folder 14)
    - What Shall We Tell Caroline?, 1961-1962 (Box 612, Folder 15)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf, 1974-1975 (Box 612, Folder 16)
    - The Wild Duck, 1985-1986 (Box 612, Folder 17)
    - Production Photos-The Wild Duck-Photos by George de Vincent, 1985-1986 (Box 612, Folder 18)
    - Winter's Tale, 1979 (Box 612, Folder 19)
    - Wipe Out Games, 1970-1971 (Box 613, Folder 1)
    - Witness for the Prosecution, 1957 (Box 613, Folder 2)
    - Women and Water, 1985-1986 (Box 613, Folder 3)
    - Women and Water, 1985-1986 (Box 613, Folder 4)
    - The World of Sholom Aleichem, 1955 (Box 613, Folder 5)
    - Woza Albert!, 1984-1985 (Box 613, Folder 6)
    - You Can't Take It With You, 1969-1970 (Box 613, Folder 7)
    - You Can't Take It With You, 1979-1980 (Box 613, Folder 8)
    - Zalmen, or the Madness of God, 1973-1974 (Box 613, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 3.2: Production books, 1963-1989
    This subseries contains production photos collected in books.
    - The Affair, 1963-1964 (Box 614, Folder 1)
    - After the Fall - Arthur Miller, 1979-1980 (Box 614, Folder 2)
    - Ah! Wilderness! - Eugene O'Neill, 1978-1979 (Box 614, Folder 3)
    - American Buffalo - David Mammet, 1980-1981 (Box 614, Folder 4)
    - An American Tragedy, 1979-1980 (Box 614, Folder 5)
    - An American Tragedy - Anthony Giardina, 1979-1980 (Box 615, Folder 1)
    - The Autumn Garden - Lillian Hellman, 1976-1977 (Box 615, Folder 2)
    - Billy Budd - Louise O Coxe and Robert Chapman, 1964-1965 (Box 615, Folder 3)
    - Buried Child - Sam Shepard, 1982-1983 (Box 615, Folder 4)
    - Catsplay - Istvan Orkeny adapted by Clara Gyorgyey, 1976-1977 (Box 615, Folder 5)
    - The Child (Part of the Carousel of New Plays) - Anthony Giardina, 1980-1981 (Box 616, Folder 1)
    - Chorus of Disapproval - Alan Ayckbourn, 1988-1989 (Box 616, Folder 2)
    - Comedians - Trevor Griffiths, 1977-1978 (Box 616, Folder 3)
    - Comedians - Trevor Griffiths, 1977-1979 (Box 616, Folder 4)
    - The Crucible - Arthur Miller, 1986-1987 (Box 616, Folder 5)
    - Curse of the Starving Class - Sam Shepard, 1978-1979 (Box 616, Folder 6)
    - Dark of the Moon - Howard Richardson and William Berney, 1963-1964 (Box 617, Folder 1)
    - A Delicate Balance - Edward Albee, 1981-1982 (Box 617, Folder 2)
    - A Delicate Balance - Edward Albee, 1981-1982 (Box 617, Folder 3)
    - Design for Living - Noel Coward, 1979-1980 (Box 617, Folder 4)
    - Design for Living - Noel Coward, 1979-1980 (Box 617, Folder 5)
    - The Devils - John Whiting, 1963-1964 (Box 618, Folder 1)
    - Don Juan - Moliere, 1978-1979 (Box 618, Folder 2)
    - The Dybbuk - S. Ansky, Adapted by John Hirsch, 1974-1975 (Box 618, Folder 3)
    - Emigres - Siawomir Mrozek (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 618, Folder 4)
    - Emigres - Siawomir Mrozek (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 618, Folder 5)
    - An Enemy of the People - John P. Vincent, 1975-1976 (Box 619, Folder 1)
    - Galileo - Bertolt Brecht - Charles Laughton (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 619, Folder 2)
    - Galileo - Bertolt Brecht - Charles Laughton (2 of 2), 1980-1982 (Box 619, Folder 3)
    - Gemini - Albert Innaurato (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 619, Folder 4)
    - Gemini - Albert Innaurato (2 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box 619, Folder 5)
    - Geniuses - Jonathan Reynolds, 1982-1983 (Box 620, Folder 1)
    - God Bless You, Mr. Rosewater - Kurt Vonnegut, 1980-1981 (Box 620, Folder 2)
    - Hamlet, 1977-1978 (Box 620, Folder 3)
    - Heartbreak House, Undated (Box 620, Folder 4)
    - A History of American Film, 1976-1977 (Box 620, Folder 5)
    - Hotel Paradiso - Adapt. Peter Glenville, 1963-1964 (Box 621, Folder 1)
    - The Imaginary Invalid - Moliere, 1982-1983 (Box 621, Folder 2)
    - The Imaginary Invalid - Moliere, 1982-1984 (Box 621, Folder 3)
    - Indians - Arthur Kopit, 1968-1969 (Box 621, Folder 4)
    - Idiot's Delight - Robert Sherwood, 1978-1979 (Box 621, Folder 5)
    - Idiot's Delight - Robert Sherwood, 1978-1980 (Box 622, Folder 1)
    - Julius Caesar, 1974-1975 (Box 622, Folder 2)
    - Kean, 1980-1981 (Box 622, Folder 3)
    - K2 - Patrick Meyers, 1981-1982 (Box 622, Folder 4)
    - A Lesson From Aloes - Sam Shepard, 1988-1989 (Box 622, Folder 5)
    - A Lie of the Mind, 1988-1989 (Box 622, Folder 6)
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night - E. O'Neill, 1975-1976 (Box 623, Folder 1)
    - Loose Ends - Michael Weller, 1978-1977 (Box 623, Folder 2)
    - The Lower Depths, 1976-1977 (Box 623, Folder 3)
    - The Madness of God - Elie Wiesel, 1973-1974 (Box 623, Folder 4)
    - Major Barbara, 1981-1982 (Box 624, Folder 1)
    - The Man Who Came to Dinner, 1980-1981 (Box 624, Folder 2)
    - The Moon in the Yellow River, 1961-1962 (Box 624, Folder 3)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 624, Folder 4)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (2 of 2), 1981-1983 (Box 624, Folder 5)
    - The National Health - Peter Nichols, 1977-1978 (Box 625, Folder 1)
    - Nightclub Cantata - Elizabeth Swados, 1977-1978 (Box 625, Folder 2)
    - Once in a Lifetime, 1975-1976 (Box 625, Folder 3)
    - Once in a Lifetime, 1975-1977 (Box 625, Folder 4)
    - One Mo' Time, 1980-1981 (Box 626, Folder 1)
    - On the Razzle - Tom Stoppard, 1982-1983 (Box 626, Folder 2)
    - Pantomime - Derek Walcott, 1980-1981 (Box 626, Folder 3)
    - Passion Play - Peter Nichols, 1984-1985 (Box 626, Folder 4)
    - The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat (1 of 2 ), 1968-1969 (Box 626, Folder 5)
    - The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat (2 of 2), 1968-1970 (Box 626, Folder 6)
    - Screen Play - Gita Honegger and Zelda Fichandler, 1982-1983 (Box 627, Folder 1)
    - Serjeant Musgrave's Dance - John Arden, 1965-1966 (Box 627, Folder 2)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1968-1969 (Box 627, Folder 3)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1968-1969 (Box 627, Folder 4)
    - Serjeant Musgrave's Dance - John Arden, 1965-1966 (Box 628, Folder 1)
    - Streamers - David Rabe, 1976-1977 (Box 628, Folder 2)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire - Tennessee Williams (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 628, Folder 3)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire - Tennessee Williams (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 628, Folder 4)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 629, Folder 1)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods (2 of 2), 1978-1978 (Box 629, Folder 2)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 1963-1964 (Box 629, Folder 3)
    - Teibele and Her Demon, 1979-1980 (Box 629, Folder 4)
    - Tin Types: A Ragtime Revue, 1978-1979 (Box 629, Folder 5)
    - Tom - Alexander Buzo, 1973-1974 (Box 630, Folder 1)
    - Tomfoolery, 1981-1982 (Box 630, Folder 2)
    - The Tot Family, 1975-1976 (Box 630, Folder 3)
    - Two by Samuel Beckett, 1973-1974 (Box 630, Folder 4)
    - Undiscovered Country by Arthur Schnitzler (Folder 1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 631, Folder 1)
    - Undiscovered Country by Arthur Schnitzler (Folder 2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 631, Folder 2)
    - The Wall by Millard Lampell, 1963-1964 (Box 631, Folder 3)
    - The Winter's Tale (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 631, Folder 4)
    - The Winter's Tale (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 631, Folder 5)
    - You Can't Take It With You by George S. Kaufman and Moss Hart (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 632, Folder 1)
    - You Can't Take It With You by George S. Kaufman and Moss Hart (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 632, Folder 2)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour by Walter Jones, 1978-1979 (Box 632, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3.3: Buildings, staff, and events, 1950-1990s
    This subseries includes photographs of Arena's buildings, staff and cast portraits, and event photographs.